[{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664032999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":9312,"timeElapsed":52907},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664041060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":8059,"timeElapsed":60968},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664050530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":9469,"timeElapsed":70438},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664056931,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":6399,"timeElapsed":76839},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664063581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":6649,"timeElapsed":83489},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664069391,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5808,"timeElapsed":89299},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664073111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3719,"timeElapsed":93019},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664078742,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5629,"timeElapsed":98650},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664082232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3489,"timeElapsed":102140},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664093892,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9979,"timeElapsed":113800},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664097473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3579,"timeElapsed":117381},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664102283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4809,"timeElapsed":122191},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664105783,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3499,"timeElapsed":125691},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664109193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3409,"timeElapsed":129101},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664113423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4229,"timeElapsed":133331},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664118183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4759,"timeElapsed":138091},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664121024,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2839,"timeElapsed":140932},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664123174,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"236","question":"Choose one item of clothing you are currently wearing and describe how you came to own this item.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2149,"timeElapsed":143082},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664130124,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5649,"timeElapsed":150032},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664135944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":5819,"timeElapsed":155852},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664139144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3199,"timeElapsed":159052},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664142455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":3309,"timeElapsed":162362},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664145985,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3529,"timeElapsed":165893},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664148845,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2859,"timeElapsed":168753},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664152615,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3769,"timeElapsed":172523},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664156065,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":3449,"timeElapsed":175973},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664159435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"167","question":"Do you have any plants? How good are you at keeping them alive?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3369,"timeElapsed":179343},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664175517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":14649,"timeElapsed":195425},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664178587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3069,"timeElapsed":198495},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664181708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3119,"timeElapsed":201615},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664184227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":204135},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664186208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1979,"timeElapsed":206116},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664188688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2479,"timeElapsed":208596},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664191428,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2739,"timeElapsed":211336},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664193857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2428,"timeElapsed":213765},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664198618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"10","question":"If you could change anything about the way you were raised, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4759,"timeElapsed":218526},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664205919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6299,"timeElapsed":225827},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664208949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3029,"timeElapsed":228857},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664212859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":3909,"timeElapsed":232767},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664215549,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":2689,"timeElapsed":235457},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664217789,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2239,"timeElapsed":237697},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664219639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1849,"timeElapsed":239547},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664222120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":2479,"timeElapsed":242028},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664224610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":2489,"timeElapsed":244518},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664227070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"13","question":"If a crystal ball could tell you the truth about yourself, your life, the future, or anything else, what would you want to know?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":2459,"timeElapsed":246978},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664233170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":4379,"timeElapsed":253078},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664235050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1879,"timeElapsed":254958},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664237870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2819,"timeElapsed":257778},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664240601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2729,"timeElapsed":260509},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664247881,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7279,"timeElapsed":267789},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664250700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2818,"timeElapsed":270608},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664252701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2000,"timeElapsed":272609},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664255631,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2929,"timeElapsed":275539},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664258032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":277940},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664260672,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2639,"timeElapsed":280580},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664266702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5059,"timeElapsed":286610},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664269832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3129,"timeElapsed":289740},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664272452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2619,"timeElapsed":292360},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664274432,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":1979,"timeElapsed":294340},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664276652,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2219,"timeElapsed":296560},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664279433,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2779,"timeElapsed":299340},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664281853,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":301761},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664284364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2509,"timeElapsed":304272},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664287254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2889,"timeElapsed":307162},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664295594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6819,"timeElapsed":315502},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664300044,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4449,"timeElapsed":319952},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664302654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2609,"timeElapsed":322562},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664304925,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2269,"timeElapsed":324832},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664307734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2809,"timeElapsed":327642},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664310254,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":330162},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664313914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3659,"timeElapsed":333822},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664316784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2869,"timeElapsed":336692},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2039,"timeElapsed":338732},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664326465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":6589,"timeElapsed":346372},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664328895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2429,"timeElapsed":348803},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664331145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2249,"timeElapsed":351053},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664333565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":353473},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664335455,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1888,"timeElapsed":355363},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664337785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2329,"timeElapsed":357693},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664343106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5319,"timeElapsed":363014},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664345336,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":2229,"timeElapsed":365244},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664351346,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6008,"timeElapsed":371254},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2129,"timeElapsed":373384},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664357806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3349,"timeElapsed":377714},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664362837,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5029,"timeElapsed":382745},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664365677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2839,"timeElapsed":385585},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664368097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":388005},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664370437,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2338,"timeElapsed":390345},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664373117,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2679,"timeElapsed":393025},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664376707,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3589,"timeElapsed":396615},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664379647,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2939,"timeElapsed":399555},{"subjectID":"gbauqmlk5d","prolificID":"63fcf26a814570a76bcf2237","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"677421600060f6cfd67ed9b2","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664383907,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"119","question":"What is your biggest insecurity?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":99,"rt":4259,"timeElapsed":403815}]